# SANTIAGO TORRES AYALA

**4** +34 665 67 07 91

Tres Cantos, Madrid - Spain

in linkedin.com/in/santiago-torres-ayala/

github.com/santiagoTorres27

santiagotorres27.github.io/My-Portfolio/

Front-End Developer and Graphic Designer. I am passionate about software development. I enjoy learning new technologies and improving my programming expertise every day. I would like to be part of a team where I can contribute with the skills I have and at the same time learn and acquire new knowledge in order to become a competent and qualified professional.

## **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2022

### **Associate Degree in Web Development**

Centro Profesional José Ramón Otero, Madrid

2019 - 2021

#### **Associate Degree in Mobile Development**

Universidad Europea, Madrid

2010 - 2016

#### **Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Design**

Pontificia Universidad Católica del Ecuador

# **EXPERIENCE**

**April 2022 - June 2022** 

**Bosonit - Madrid** 

Internship in Front-End department, with training in technologies such as SQL, HTML, SCSS and Angular.

#### April 2021 - June 2021

**VASS - Madrid** 

Internship in Artificial Intelligence Department with Python development tasks and sample data labeling for training different Machine Leaning (NLP) models on AWS.

# **December 2016 - July 2019**

**Graphic Designer and Illustrator** 

Freelance, Ecuador

# **SKILLS**

Spring Framework JavaScript CSS Android Studio SASS TypeScript Angular Python Bootstrap Adobe Illustrator React SQL HTML Adobe Photoshop lava

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish (Native) - English (B2)